Christina D'Agostino

Sewell, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Christina-D'Agostino/d177a64891214467

Registered pharmacist in the states of New Jersey and Pennsylvania with 22 years experience in retail pharmacy

Excellent communication skills, Exceptional ability to master new skills and situations, Enthusiastic and motivated employee with demonstrated ability to: Handle a variety of responsibilities, Communicate effectively with all levels of management/oversee personnel, Master new technology, Meet and exceed heavy workloads independently.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Care Pharmacist

Wedgewood Pharmacy - Swedesboro, NJ - November 2012 to Present

Check prescriptions in a speciality compounding pharmacy.

Registered Pharmacist

CVS PHARMACY - Mount Ephraim, NJ - December 2008 to September 2011

Checks prescriptions for correct dosage and for drug interactions and incompatibilities Compounds prescribed medicines and packages and labels them. Records prescriptions dispensed, and the issue of poisons, narcotics and other restricted drugs Provides advice and information on the use and effects of medications interpret and fill physicians' prescriptions for customers on a daily basis Verify all patient information before filling a prescription Provide medicinal consultation to customers upon filling a prescription and on OTC (over the counter) medicines as required Perform order entry of prescriptions into the required pharmacy database Contact physicians and benefits providers as necessary to process a prescription Complete third-party insurance forms and other paperwork Provide a professional and confidential environment for customers on all occasions. Compound medications when necessary. I am also a licensed immunizer and certified in CPR.

Registered Pharmacist

CVS PHARMACY - Blackwood, NJ - December 2007 to December 2008

Responsible for routine duties in high volume pharmacy

Registered Pharmacist

ECKERD PHARMACY - Deptford, NJ - February 2002 to December 2007

Responsible for compounding, patient counseling, patient, profile maintenance, In a store filling approximately 3, 000 prescriptions weekly.

Registered Pharmacist

CVS PHARMACY - Sewell, NJ - October 1989 to February 2002

Responsible for routine duties in a high volume pharmacy

ORGANIZTIONS

NJSHP (New Jersey Society of Health-System Pharmacist)

EDUCATION

BS in Pharmacy

Temple University School of Pharmacy Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA May 1992